Speaker: The Fortune Teller
Part 1
One night in London, a young police inspector called McCleary had a conversation with his wife.
"My dear," said McCleary.
"I can’t stop thinking about our neighbor, Mrs. Myers.
I’d love to know how she makes her money.
She lives so luxuriously – she even buys asparagus in the winter!"
"Leave it to me," said Mrs. McCleary.
"I have an idea."
The next day, she dressed like a younger woman,
took off her wedding ring, and went to visit Mrs. Myers.
"Sit down, my child," said Mrs. Myers.
"What can I do for you?"
"I’m going to be 20 tomorrow.
I want to know what’s going to happen to me in the future."
Mrs. Myers picked up a deck of cards and began to shuffle them.
"You are Miss…?"
"Jones," said Mrs. McCleary, very quietly.
"My dear Miss Jones," said Mrs. Myers.
"Please take five cards and put them on the table face down."